securew2.com 2019-04-20

# Privacy Policy | SecureW2

* * *

If you have any questions regarding privacy on our website, feel free to contact us at [privacy@securew2.com](mailto:privacy@securew2.com).

Privacy and security is very important to SecureW2. As such, we have outlined the ways that we may collect your information and the uses of collected information in the following privacy policy.

#### Voluntarily Provided Information

Personal information provided by users on the website, usually through the submission of forms or the use of services and trials, is collected and stored. The information gathered this way is used for direct communication and servicing of accounts, as well as distributing trial software and verifying identity. Without this information it would be impossible to properly assist you. Information collected this way includes identity, company information, contact information, and infrastructure details for deployments. This data is protected and never shared outside of the company except in cases when used to help us serve your account.

Occasionally, information provided may be used when creating testimonials or case studies. In these situations, you will explicitly be asked for permission.

#### Promotional Communications

Occasionally, we send out promotional communications based on information provided. These emails fall outside of the scope of normal customer service emails and may include newsletters, special offers, or news. We only send out emails we believe will provide value to you based on the information we have. A link will be included in all promotional emails that will let you change the types of emails you receive, or opt-out altogether. To opt-out of any other form of promotional communications, please send an email to [privacy@securew2.com](mailto:privacy@securew2.com). Please note that it may take several business days to process requests.

#### Passively Collected Information

In addition to information provided voluntarily by users, our website also passively collects information from a variety of sources. This information is used to better understand our visitors and improve the quality of our services. As with most websites, SecureW2 uses log files to track visitors – a standard practice on the web. Information collected includes IP addresses, date and time, browser types, Internet Service Providers, and the pages visited. We may also keep track of user email information, such as whether you have opened an email or forwarded it.

**Cookies**

SecureW2.com uses cookies to supplement information provided by the log files. Cookies are little pieces of anonymous data that help our site remember who you are next time you visit. These help create better and more seamless website experiences. Cookies are managed by your internet browser, and you can find more information online about how to change the default browser cookie settings.

**Web Beacon**

In addition to cookies, our website may deliver web beacons, which are clear GIF images that are loaded as part of a page. These images help give us more detailed information about how visitors are using our website. Unlike cookies, they are not stored on your hard drive.

Information collected passively will never include contact information or the browsing history of other websites. The data is restricted to information provided by your browser’s session and history on our website.

#### Third Party Privacy Policies

Occasionally, Securew2.com links to other websites. These websites are covered by their own privacy policy.

#### Behavioral Advertising

Some of the behavioral information provided will be used to customize advertisements provided by third party partners, including Adroll and Google. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. _ _ If you wish to opt-out of targeted advertisements, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

#### Children’s Information

SecureW2 is not interested in, and does not knowingly collect information of minors. If a parent or guardian believes that we have any identification information of a child under the age of 13, contact us immediately to have it removed from our records.

#### Offline Data Collection

This privacy policy only applies to data gathered from this website. We may also collect and aggregate data from other sources.

#### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

### Last Updated: 4/8/2015
